<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Telegram on Miquel's Portfolio</title><link>https://miquelt.me/portfolio/tags/telegram/</link><description>Recent content in Telegram on Miquel's Portfolio</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 06:00:23 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://miquelt.me/portfolio/tags/telegram/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Otaniemi Tracker Bot</title><link>https://miquelt.me/portfolio/posts/personal/otaniemi-tracker-bot/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 06:00:23 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://miquelt.me/portfolio/posts/personal/otaniemi-tracker-bot/</guid><description>The project On the fall semester of 2023-2024 I went abroad at Aalto University, as a Erasmus+ student I needed some place to stay during the period I was in Helsinki. However, even though me and a friend manage to get a nice apartment, we soon find out that most of the apartments rented there didn&amp;rsquo;t have any furtniture and people brought their own. Unfortunately as exchange students we couldn&amp;rsquo;t just rent a van a bring our bed, table and chair from the other side of Europe.</description></item><item><title>λ-Calculus Telegram Bot</title><link>https://miquelt.me/portfolio/posts/college/lambdacalculustelegrambot/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 06:00:23 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://miquelt.me/portfolio/posts/college/lambdacalculustelegrambot/</guid><description>The statement The task was to build a lambda calculus interpreter. The interpreter also requiered to support the definition and use of macros. The interpreter had to run as a Telegram bot. It was needed that the bot could support sending the image of the tree interpratated, do ß-reductions and α-conversions.
The full statement can be found below or in the following site (in Catalan).
More than a complex project this just requiered spending time on making sure all the requierements were added after understanding how λ calculus works.</description></item></channel></rss>