<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Scikit-Learn on Miquel's Portfolio</title><link>https://miquelt.me/portfolio/tags/scikit-learn/</link><description>Recent content in Scikit-Learn on Miquel's Portfolio</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 06:00:23 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://miquelt.me/portfolio/tags/scikit-learn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ecoforecast</title><link>https://miquelt.me/portfolio/posts/competitions/ecoforecast/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 06:00:23 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://miquelt.me/portfolio/posts/competitions/ecoforecast/</guid><description>The challenge With increasing digitalisation and the growing on data servers, the significance of sustainable computing is on the rise. That&amp;rsquo;s why the task is to predict which will be the European contry that will have the highest surplus of green energy in the following hour. Knowing this information can be critical to make important decisions in order to reduce CO2 emissions. This challenge was the problem of a Nuwe competition.</description></item><item><title>JBarcelona 2023</title><link>https://miquelt.me/portfolio/posts/competitions/jobbarcelona2023/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 06:00:23 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://miquelt.me/portfolio/posts/competitions/jobbarcelona2023/</guid><description>The challenge This challenge was the problem of a Nuwe competition. The goal of the challenge was to build a classification model which had to predict which costumers decide to end their contracts with the company we get the data from, so the percentage of people who stop being clients decreses by analyzing the reasons.
The approach Since this was my first time building a model, I decided to start by looking at some guides and understand what had to exactly do the model.</description></item><item><title>HackUPC 2023</title><link>https://miquelt.me/portfolio/posts/competitions/hackupc2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 06:00:23 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://miquelt.me/portfolio/posts/competitions/hackupc2023/</guid><description>Our project HackUPC is the main yearly hackathon organized in my university. In 2023 was my first time attending on site.
Me, AlexRG03, Martaw-code and Koldp took part at the competition. We were very indecisive in terms of which challenge to go for, but in the end we decided to work in the HP challenge, in which we had to build a prediction model to forecast the supply chain inventory units of HP.</description></item></channel></rss>