<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Python on Miquel's Portfolio</title><link>https://miquelt.me/portfolio/tags/python/</link><description>Recent content in Python on Miquel's Portfolio</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 06:00:23 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://miquelt.me/portfolio/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ecoforecast</title><link>https://miquelt.me/portfolio/posts/competitions/ecoforecast/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 06:00:23 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://miquelt.me/portfolio/posts/competitions/ecoforecast/</guid><description>The challenge With increasing digitalisation and the growing on data servers, the significance of sustainable computing is on the rise. That&amp;rsquo;s why the task is to predict which will be the European contry that will have the highest surplus of green energy in the following hour. Knowing this information can be critical to make important decisions in order to reduce CO2 emissions. This challenge was the problem of a Nuwe competition.</description></item><item><title>Otaniemi Tracker Bot</title><link>https://miquelt.me/portfolio/posts/personal/otaniemi-tracker-bot/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 06:00:23 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://miquelt.me/portfolio/posts/personal/otaniemi-tracker-bot/</guid><description>The project On the fall semester of 2023-2024 I went abroad at Aalto University, as a Erasmus+ student I needed some place to stay during the period I was in Helsinki. However, even though me and a friend manage to get a nice apartment, we soon find out that most of the apartments rented there didn&amp;rsquo;t have any furtniture and people brought their own. Unfortunately as exchange students we couldn&amp;rsquo;t just rent a van a bring our bed, table and chair from the other side of Europe.</description></item><item><title>λ-Calculus Telegram Bot</title><link>https://miquelt.me/portfolio/posts/college/lambdacalculustelegrambot/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 06:00:23 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://miquelt.me/portfolio/posts/college/lambdacalculustelegrambot/</guid><description>The statement The task was to build a lambda calculus interpreter. The interpreter also requiered to support the definition and use of macros. The interpreter had to run as a Telegram bot. It was needed that the bot could support sending the image of the tree interpratated, do ß-reductions and α-conversions.
The full statement can be found below or in the following site (in Catalan).
More than a complex project this just requiered spending time on making sure all the requierements were added after understanding how λ calculus works.</description></item><item><title>JBarcelona 2023</title><link>https://miquelt.me/portfolio/posts/competitions/jobbarcelona2023/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 06:00:23 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://miquelt.me/portfolio/posts/competitions/jobbarcelona2023/</guid><description>The challenge This challenge was the problem of a Nuwe competition. The goal of the challenge was to build a classification model which had to predict which costumers decide to end their contracts with the company we get the data from, so the percentage of people who stop being clients decreses by analyzing the reasons.
The approach Since this was my first time building a model, I decided to start by looking at some guides and understand what had to exactly do the model.</description></item><item><title>HackUPC 2023</title><link>https://miquelt.me/portfolio/posts/competitions/hackupc2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 06:00:23 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://miquelt.me/portfolio/posts/competitions/hackupc2023/</guid><description>Our project HackUPC is the main yearly hackathon organized in my university. In 2023 was my first time attending on site.
Me, AlexRG03, Martaw-code and Koldp took part at the competition. We were very indecisive in terms of which challenge to go for, but in the end we decided to work in the HP challenge, in which we had to build a prediction model to forecast the supply chain inventory units of HP.</description></item><item><title>Chips-Chips</title><link>https://miquelt.me/portfolio/posts/competitions/funcions-numerables/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 06:00:23 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://miquelt.me/portfolio/posts/competitions/funcions-numerables/</guid><description>The challenge The goal of this challenge was to minimize the average length of chains that connected pins in a chip, while also trying to minimize the standard deviation of the lengths of the different chains. This was a problem set by Qualcomm for the FME Datathon 2022 which had the aim of minimizing the power loss across a chip.
Our approach Together with Paula, Ruth, Àlex and I, we decided to approach the problem by modelling it by considering a graph where the nodes are pins and the edges cables.</description></item></channel></rss>